GREGORY MENO

phone 407 493 3734

location 29 Wiltshire dr. Avondale Estates, GA 30002

email greg.meno@gmail.com

online https://github.com/GregMeno

TECHNOLOGIES

HTTP, REST, AJAX JSON, XML, SQL

python erlang javascript c, c++ Perl. PHP

CouchDB, mongoDB Celery, RabbitMQ memcached django, Flask

Solr, Haystack, Tastypie

node.js IRC GTK, Qt

Postgres, SQLite

AWS

SOFTWARE

Linux, MacOS git, svn vim pyflakes, fugitive dpkg, apt pdb, strace xchat jira, trac, Review Board bash, sed

COMMUNITY

member PyATL member CLUG member StackOverflow attended pyCon2011 attended pyCon2010

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida, Orlando BS, Computer Science 2005

REFERENCES

upon request

PROFILE

My python knowledge is strong and I can learn new technology with speed and ease. My professional experience covers eight years programming in Linux and Unix-like environments. I have worked as an individual, part of a team, and in a mentor role. From this experience I am confident that I can communicate with all types of people.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer, CMGd Atlanta, GA

6/2010 - Present

I work on a team of more than thirty dev-ops who are building a massive Django CMS. I maintain an ubuntu virtualbox image and setup scripts containing all that is necessary to start contributing to our CMS in an hour or less. Over the course of a year I presented four lunch and learns on a variety of technical topics. I co-taught a six session class for all members of our team on proper unit-testing. I am directly responsible for the mentoring of a developer who is new to the software industry. My advice on matters relating to python, Linux, and git are highly sought after. Recently I have lead an effort to improve and simplify the ad management system that enables our advertising team to generate a large portion of our revenue.

Software Engineer, IDEAL Technology Orlando, FL

10/2005 - 6/2010

I worked on development, operations, and testing on STRIKETM a digital media exploitation device. I played a key part on the four man team who designed and built this system which was initially delivered in six months. My influence brought functional specification to our development cycle. I have leveraged open source libraries to create custom filesystem drivers in userspace. My pyGTK code that I wrote allows users to customize the way STRIKE extracts and analyzes data as well as view that data intuitively. I configured Fluxbox to enable our system to operate like a kiosk. I designed and wrote a process that is used to provide in-field updates to our customers. In this position Also, I mentored junior developers by giving talks, reviewing their code, providing constructive feedback, and sizing tasks appropriately.

Programmer, International Aviation Advisors Orlando, FL

4/2003 - 12/2004

My responsibility was to maintain and modify an online value forecast simulation written in c and Perl. My duties included code verification, web application development, and scripting tests.

Jr. Systems Administrator, Quasar.net Orlando, FL

1/2002 - 2/2003

I Managed and maintained debian based Linux web servers. I wrote scripts in Perl to facilitate bandwidth reporting.